rlmseo.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Cincinnati SEO, Web Design, PPC by Razorlight Media

Your privacy is important to us. That’s why we will never share your contact information with any third parties unless you want us to. We also hate spam just as much as you do and will never use your email address for anything other than what you tell us is ok.

Razorlight Media is committed to your privacy and your rights as our customer. Any information gathered by Razorlight Media will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used or shared in ways for which you have specifically consented. The following statement discloses our standard practice regarding the information we collect and the information we hold on behalf of our customers.

This privacy policy only applies to the Razorlight Media website. The privacy policy applies to information that is given offline as well as on the Razorlight Media website. The policy does not pertain to third party web sites that are accessible through Razorlight Media’ website. Razorlight Media proposes that you read the privacy policies of any third party site to learn how they collect and use information that is gathered.

## Information gathered online

Subscribe to any of Razorlight Media’ Newsletters – Email address (required) and other optional data such as First and Last Name, Company or Organization and phone number are gathered when you subscribe to any of Razorlight Media’s Newsletters.

Webinars – Razorlight Media may collect information from you for the purposes of tracking webinar participants as well as to follow up and get feedback from participants, as well as notify participants of promotional offers. All information requested is optional. Information may include, but is not limited to, First and Last Name, Company or Organization, information requested, and whether or not participants would like to receive newsletters or special offers via email. Supplying Razorlight Media, whether verbally or in writing, with any information constitutes your agreement for Razorlight Media to contact you through email, telephone, or postal mail for marketing purposes.

Contact Us – You are directed to send an Email to a specific department within Razorlight Media. Through this process your Name, Email Address and Comment or Question are collected. This information is only used to respond to your question or suggestion and to follow up in the future if there is no response or if you request a future contact attempt.

Technical Information – Upon visiting the website, Razorlight Media may collect log file data on your session. This technical information alone does not identify a specific individual. The information collected may include (but is not limited to): The URL of the site that you came from before visiting Razorlight Media’ website. Your computer’s IP address. The browser you are using. The pages that you visit on the Razorlight Media website. Search terms that are used on the Razorlight Media website. There is no merging of technical and personal data collected on the site. Technical information is used to measure and improve the effectiveness of the Razorlight Media website and diagnose problems and is not used to gather personal information about you in any way.

Contests or Sweepstakes – When you enter a sweepstakes or other promotional event on Razorlight Media’ website, we may ask for your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can administer the sweepstakes and notify winners. By entering contests or sweepstakes you agree to be notified of promotional offers via email, telephone, or postal mail. You can always opt out of receiving any promotional offers when submitting information or by unsubscribing to such offers.

## Information gathered offline

Any information you submit to Razorlight Media in any form that is not online will be stored in a secure location and never shared with any third parties unless necessary for your project, or if requested or authorized by you. Information shared with a third party for purposes related to your project will be kept to a minimum level that is necessary to ensure proper completion of the task. The level of information that is considered a “minimum level” will be determined exclusively by Razorlight Media.

## Customer Data

Through the various services provided by our software we also collect and store information in a secure and private manner on behalf of our customers. This information includes, but is not limited to, email address lists, articles, survey answers, letters, and usage statistics. This information is owned by Razorlight Media and is not accessible to our partners or other customers unless the customer grants permission.

## Use of Cookies

Our sites may use cookies to authenticate the user and keep track of the user session. Cookies are used to allow you to enter the portions of the Razorlight Media website reserved for registered customers (users). Razorlight Media does not use cookies to collect any information about you. We also use cookies to govern over survey voting.

## Use of Web Beacons

Web beacons are used in combination with cookies. A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, which is placed in an email or on a website. Razorlight Media uses web beacons to aggregate data that is used to analyze the performance of an email and related sites. The information collected can be correlated to individual subscribers. This data is used for internal Razorlight Media marketing purposes only. Open rates and click through rates for email content are examples of the metrics that are calculated using web beacons.

## Our Partners and Third Parties

Razorlight Media may share information with partners or third parties during the process of any transaction with Razorlight Media. The information shared is for the purpose of completion of your design or marketing project. Supplying Razorlight Media with any information constitutes your consent for Razorlight Media to share said information if it deems necessary for the purpose of completing, or expiditing the completion of your project.

## Control and Modification of Third Parties

You remain in control of your information. When you provide your information you can select whether you want to receive further communications about our products and services or other marketing information. When you opt-in to receive marketing communications from Razorlight Media, you can opt-out whenever you want. There is an opt-out feature located in the footer of all Mirage Design Works marketing email list communications. Razorlight Media wants your personal data to be accurate and complete. If you want to change any of the personal data or preferences you can contact us here, or call (513) 549-7355.

## Data Security

This site does not have security measures in place. Any information that you do not wish to share with a third party should not be submitted anywhere on the Razorlight Media website. Any information that you do submit may be viewed by a third party and is not the responsibility of Razorlight Media.

## Questions and Contact Information

If you have any questions about this privacy Policy, you can contact us here. Or, send correspondence to the following address:

> Razorlight Media  
> 700 West Pete Rose Way, #68  
> Cincinnati, OH 45203  
> United States of America

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Changes to the privacy policy will be posted in this section. This way you will always have a clear understanding of what information is collected online and offline, how it is used, and the choices you have. Your personal information will only be used in accordance with the version of the Policy that is in place at the time that you provided your information, unless you provide your consent to do otherwise.

We hope you enjoy your experience here! If you’d like more information about Razorlight Media, or to request a free consultation, feel free to contact us today.

If you’re new here and haven’t read our newsletter, subscribe for free and receive the techniques we use everyday to market our clients’ sites delivered directly to your inbox twice a month. Find out more about your free subscription here.

Looking for cincinnati web design services? Or perhaps WordPress SEO? We can help. Get in touch with us for a free, no obligation quote or view our services section for more information about how we can help you acheive your goals.
